You will never see it coming.
Phantom is a thriller film directed by Todd Robinson.
The haunted Captain of a Soviet submarine holds
the fate of the world in his hands.
Forced to leave his family behind, he is charged with
leading a covert mission cloaked in mystery.
Demi, played by Ed Harris.
Bruni, played by David Duchovny.
Markov, played by Lance Henriksen.
Alex, played by William Fichtner.
Pavlov, played by Johnathon Schaech.
Semak, played by Jason Beghe.
Phantom is a 2013 American submarine thriller film about a
Soviet submarine during the Cold War in the 1960s.
Todd Robinson wrote and directed the film.
It stars Ed Harris, David Duchovny and William Fichtner.
The film tells the story of a Soviet Navy submarine
captain attempting to prevent a war.
It is loosely based on the real-life events involving the
sinking of the submarine K-129 in 1968.
The film explores themes of submarine, cold war, soviet union.
The tone is intense.